Guide to the Irving Godt Papers 1952-2002 (Bulk 1970-1992) MC 206
New York University Archives
- Series VII: Marianna Martines research material
  - Subseries A: Musical Scores
    - In Exitu Florence Part 2 of 2, Undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - In Exitu, ONB, Part 1 of 2, Undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - In Exitu, ONB, Part 2 of 2, Undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - In Exitu Transcript, Undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Isacco Sinfonia, 1781 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Keyboard Concerto in A, Transcription, Undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Keyboard Concerto in C, Transcription, Undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Keyboard Concertn in C, Transcription, Undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - La Tempesta, 1778 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Laudate Part 1 of 2, Undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Laudate Part 2 of 2, Undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Laudate, Transcribed, Undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Litania della B.V in D Major, 1762 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Litany in D Major, 1762 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Litany in D Transcript, 1762 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Litany in G, 1775 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Litany in G Transcript, 1775 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Lodate Transcription and Parts, Undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Sheet Music, 1768, Undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Miserere, 1769 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Miserere Acapella, 1768 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Miserere bound transcript, 1769 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Miserere, Edits, 1769 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Miserere, Italian, 1769 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Miserere mei Deus, 1768 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Miserere Naples, 1770 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Miserere, Part 1 of 2, Photos of, 1770 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Miserere, Part 2 of 2, Photos of, 1770 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Miserere Transcript, 1768 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Miserere Transcript, 1769 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Miserere Vienna, 1769 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Missa I (Part 1), Undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Missa I (Part 2), Undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Missa II (Part 1), Undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Missa II (Part 2), Undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Missa III (Part 1), Undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Missa III (Part 2), Undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Missa IV (Part 1), Undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Missa IV (Part 2), Undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Motets 1, 2, 4, Undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Motets 5-6, 1768 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Motetto 3, 1764 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Orgoglioso fiumicello, 1786 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Orgoglioso fiumicello, unedited transcript, 1786 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Overture in C, Transcript, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Overture in C Transcript and Blankenburg, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Ouverture in C, Movement III, Excerpts of, 1772 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Pieta, pieta Signore, 1769 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Quemadmodum, Undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Quemadmodum Berlin, Part I, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Quemadmodum Berlin, Part I, Transcript, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Quemadmodum Berlin, Part II, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Quemadmodum, photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Quemadmodum, Alto, Photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Quemadmodum, Basso, Photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Quemadmodum, Canto, Photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Quemadmodum, Canto Solo, Photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Quemadmodum, Corno, Photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Quemadmodum, Oboe, Photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Quemadmodum, Viola, Photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Quemadmodum, First Violin, Photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Quemadmodum, Second Violin, Photos of, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Quemadmodum with notes, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Quemadmodum and other Bologna, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, Alto Part, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, Basso Part, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, Canto Part, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, Corno Part, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, Oboe Part, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, Salerio, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, Viola Part, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, First Violin Part, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Quemadmodum Naples, Second Violin Part, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Quemadmodum Transcript, 1770 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Regina Caeli, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Regina Caeli, Transcript, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - S. Elena Symphony, Undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Salve Regina (Motet VII), with notes, Undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Salve Regina, Parts, Undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Scelta d'Arie, excerpt of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Scelte d'Arie, Vol. I, Part 1, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Scelte d'Arie, Vol. I, Part 2, B, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Scelte d'Arie, Vol. I, Part 3, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Scelte d'Arie, Vol. II, Part 1, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Scelte d'Arie, Vol. II, Part 2, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Scelte d'Arie, Vol. II, Part 3, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Scelta d'Arie Part Ia, Part 1 of 7, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Scelta d'Arie Part Ia, Part 2 of 7, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part Ia, Part 3 of 7, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part Ia, Part 4 of 7, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part Ia, Part 5 of 7, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part Ia, Part 6 of 7, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part Ia, Part 7 of 7, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part IIa, Part 1 of 6, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part IIa, Part 2 of 6, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part IIa, Part 3 of 6, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part IIa, Part 4 of 6, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part IIa, Part 5 of 6, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Scelta d'Arie, Part IIa, Part 6 of 6, Photos of, 1767 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Sonata in G, 1769 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Sonata in G with edits, 1769 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Sonata in G, Photos of, 1769 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Symphony in C, parts, 1770 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Terza Messa, 1761 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, Vol. I, part 1 of 5, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, Vol. I. part 2 of 5, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, Vol. I, part 3 of 5, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, Vol. I, part 4 of 5, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, Vol. I, part 5 of 5, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, part 1 of 7, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, part 2 of 7, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, part 3 of 7, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, part 4 of 7, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, part 5 of 7, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, part 6 of 7, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Unlabeled Martines sheet music, part 7 of 7, Photos of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Unlabeled piece of music, Undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Subseries B: Research Material
    - 18th and 19th Century Viennese Material, circa 1800s (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Annotated Martines and Contemporaries writing, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Austrian music, Articles on, Undated, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Banka Stiavnica documents, 1995, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - "Beitrage '76-'78" and "Musik am Hof", 1984 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Berggericht Substitution writing with annotations, 1835 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Bologna Letters, Martines, 1770-1790 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Book excerpt on German language, Undated (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Budova Kammerhofu, Lithograph of, Undated (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - City artwork and maps, Undated, 1809, 1824 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - City Images, Undated (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Dixit Dominus, Notes on, 1774 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - "Frau und Musik," book, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Haydn article, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Information on archival institutions, Undated (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Information on resources, Undated (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - "Jarbuch der Tonkunst von Wien und Prag," Book, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Jean Macrae Turner's research on Martines, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Lecture: "The Hunt for Marianna," audio CD, Undated (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Letter from Gerbert A. Martino and noes, excerpt, 1763 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Letters in German, 1781, 1872 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Martines coat of arms, color slide, Undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Martines and contemporaries letters and writing, circa 1770s (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Martines crest, notes on, Undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Martines letters, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Martines Portraits, Undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Martines portraits with notes, Undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Martines translated letters with notes, circa 1726-1775 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Martines writing from Milan archive, 1769-1781 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Music/Martines articles in German and Italian, Undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Notes on Martines compositions, 1768 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Photos related to Martines research, Undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Portraits and crest, negatives of, Undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Portraits and crest, photos of, Undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Portraits with notes, 1773 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Profile of Martines from internet in German, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Renaissance Music, Journal articles on, Undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Research, photo negatives, Undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Research maps, Bologna, Undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Research material, photos and artwork, Undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Research material and notes on Martines in various languages, Undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Research notes, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Research notes, Marianna's sisters, Undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Research progress reports, 1995, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Tonkunstler Society, articles on, 1871 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Transcriptions of primary correspondence and documents, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Turmer in Der Mittelslowakei, undated (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Various articles and excerpts from books, undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Vienna archive material, articles and encyclopedia entries from, undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Vienna, photos of, undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Women composers, articles on, undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Writings, Martines and contemporaries, circa 1700s (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Subseries C: Godt writings
    - Chapters 2 and 3, drafts of, Undated (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Dixit Dominus, A-R Editions article, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Dixit Dominus, A-R Editions, edits, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Dixit Dominus, review of, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Documents to serve a biography of Martines, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - "The Hunt for the Lady Marianna," draft, undated (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - "The Hunt for Marianna," Part I (Nov), draft, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - "The Hunt for Marianna," Part II (Nov), draft, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - "The Hunt for Marianna," Part I (Dec), draft, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - "The Hunt for Marianna," Part II (Dec), draft, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Intro to "The Hunt for Marianna," draft of, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Typescript, "The Hunt for Marianna," Appendix, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, "The Hunt for Marianna," Part I, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Typescript, "The Hunt for Marianna," Part II, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - "The Lady Marianna," Part I, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - "The Lady Marianna," Part II, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - "The Lady Marianna," Part IIIa, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - "The Lady Marianna," documents, Part IIIa, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - "The Lady Marianna," Part IIIb, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - "The Lady Marianna," Part I, biography, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - "The Lady Marianna," Part II, the music, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - "The Lady Marianna," Part IIIa, the documents (1), draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - "The Lady Marianna," Part IIIb, the documents (2) and appendix, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - "The Lady Marianna Von Martines," draft, Undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - "The Life and Music of Marianna Von Martines," draft, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - "Life, Family, Music," documents, drafts, Undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - "Marianna in Italy", 1995 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - "Marianna in Vienna", 1996, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - "Marianna Martinez," Academica Filarmonica Onoraria, 1994, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - "Marianna Then and Now," drafts, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Marianna Von Martines preliminary works list, Undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Marianna Von Martines: Academica Filarmonica, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Marianne Von Martines, Undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Martines bio, the documents, draft, undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Martines biography, part I, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Martines biography, part II, draft, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Martines Biography, part III, draft, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Martines biography, appendix, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Martines biography, notes to, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Martines bio, pg 16 with notes, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Martines family chronology and documents, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Specious scholarship, draft, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Tentative Martines chronology, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - "Three Painted Ladies in Bologna and one in Vienna," draft, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Memorabilia
    - Concert programs, 1995, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Tourist pamphlets, 1993, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Travel photos, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Subseries E: Correspondence
    - A-R Editions, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Ankrom, Jeff, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Appel, Fred, of Princeton University Press, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Armellini, Mario, of Civico Museo Bibliografico Musicale, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Banks, C A, of the British Library, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Biba, Otto, 1998, undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Birchler, David, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Bivash, Alberto, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Bratislava Archive, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Gesellschaft Der Musikfreunde in Wien, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Grove Press, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Guiseppe, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Hell, Helmut, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Huber, Annegret, 1996, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Klemens, Mark, of Boydell & Brewer, Inc., 2004 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Leone, Peter-John, of Indiana University Press, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Madigan, Tim, of University of Rochester Press, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Lorenz, Michael, undated (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Moravec-Hilmar, Rosemary, of the Austrian National Library, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Mraz, Gottfried, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Museen Der Stadt Wien, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Pettit, Lawrence K., 1995 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Schmalfeldt, Janet and Michael Lorenz, Undated (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Steblin, Rita, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Sven, undated (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Taylor, Judy, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Voss, Steffen, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Wolff, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Zierlinger, Veronika, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Zimmerman, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Subseries F: Oversized Material
    - Dixit Dominus, Author's proof, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Dixit Dominus, Master Proof, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - GdMF Membership list/MvM Thanks to Acc. Fil, 1773, 1812 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Hofkammer Archiv docs, circa 1770s (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Letters, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Piazza D.S. Marco, artwork, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Registry, 1812 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Ritterstand, 1774 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - "San Rocco" plate/John Bapt v. M: Military hist/ John Bapt v. M: Estate/ John Bapt. v. M: Inquest, circa 1700s (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Slovakia Docs, 2002, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Sonata in E/ Sonata in A, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Sonnleitner bio/ Probate documents, 1775, 1824 (Box 36, Folder 12)